Greg Reynolds Dance Quintet
DC Public Library, Special Collections
Greg Reynolds Dance Quintet Records
1969-1984
DC Public Library, Special Collections
5.75 linear feet; 11 boxes
022
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1: Publicity, 1972-1982
  - Publicity, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Publicity, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Publicity, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Publicity, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Series 2: Tour Files, 1979-1984
  - Arlington County Humanities Project - “Dance and Conversation”, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Australia tour, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Recital Hall performance, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chicago - Loyola University Institute of Pastoral Studies, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fairfax Council for the Arts Program for Schools, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Glen Echo Park Summer Dance Festival, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lake Placid Adirondack Festival of the Arts, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Michigan performance workshops, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Minnesota workshops, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Ohio and Kentucky, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Trinity Theater, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Wisconsin tour, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - YWCA Arts Advisory Council, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Series 3: Administrative Records, 1979-1983
  - Artist-In-Schools Program, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Awards and certificates, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Contracts, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Chronological files, 1968-1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chronological files, 1968-1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chronological files, 1968-1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files, 1968-1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files, 1968-1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dancer resumes, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Lansburgh lease, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Lansburgh plans, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Peace Through Arts Day, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Publications, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Telephone, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Omega Liturgical Dance Co., 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Series 4: Performance Programs, 1969-1975
  - Programs, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1969-1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1969-1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Series 5: Personal items, 1966-1980
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts and Humanities, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Diary excerpt, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Horoscope of Greg Reynolds, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Memorabilia, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Personal notes, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Personal correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Personal items, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Series 6: Meridian House International, 1978-1979
  - General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Japan Today - general administrative, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Japan Today - Demonstrations-In-the-School photos, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Japan Today - Essay Contest, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Japan Today - Film list, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Japan Today - General information, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Japan Today - General Resources on Japan, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Japan Today - Japan Today programs, Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Japan Today - Japan Airlines promotional materials, Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Series 7: Oversize, 1975-1981
  - Sarah Lawrence Bulletin, January 1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - GreenLake Festival of Music poster, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Crayon drawings from Mrs. Cupes 2nd grade class, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)